Definitely a curse womb.
Our window verified that
about three hours ago.
Once 90% were evacuated,
the decision was made
to seal off the center.
All citizens within
a 500 meter radius
have been evacuated as well.
I have a question.
What is this window?
It's an in-house term
for unique members of
Jujutsu Tech who can see curses
but they aren't sorcerers.
[Yuuji] Oh, okay.
Let's continue.
Detainee block two.
At present, five
detainees are still inside
along with the curse womb.
If the curse womb is the
type that metamorphose,
we predict it will become
a special grade curse spirit.
[Both] Special grade?
Hey, so I still don't
really understand
what this special grade means.
All right, allow me
to explain it idiot level.
First there's grade four, a
wooden bat is enough for them.
Grade three, if you have a
handgun, you can rest easy.
Grade two, close
call with a shotgun.
Grade one, even a
tank may be insufficient.
Then special grade, well,
you might be on even footing
if you carpet bomb
it with cluster bombs.
That is bad.
Normally, a sorcerer on
par with the cursed spirit
would handle this.
And in this case, that
would have been Gojou.
That figures.
So, where is Gojou then?
[Megumi] Away on business.
Guy like him has
better things to do
than loaf around the
school in the first place.
Don't expect any souvenirs.
Unfortunately, we're often
short handed in this business.
You'll often have to
undertake missions
beyond your expertise.
However, this current
case is an urgent one
and most of abnormal.
So no matter what, don't fight.
And if you should
encounter a special grade,
you run or you die.
(Nobara and Yuuji gasp)
Please do not
disregard your fears.
And don't forget that your
entire mission here today
is strictly the verification
and rescue of survivors.
Excuse me, sir, tell
me, where's my son?
[Security] Stay back, ma'am,
you can't come in here.
Move back, please.
Where's Tadashi?
I need to know if my
son Tadashi is all right.
[Security] Please calm down
ma'am, you must stay back.
-Please let me through.
-Its too dangerous.
She's a guardian
here for a visit.
Please leave, madam.
It's possible that someone
may have released poisonous gas
in the compound.
I'm afraid we can't share
any more details at this time.
Oh, no (crying)
Why is this happening (crying)
Fushiguro, Kugisaki,
we'll save them.
Of course.
(Megumi grunting)
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
(footsteps clicking)
Be careful.
I'll put up my veil,
emerge from
darkness blacker still
purify that which is impure.
(veil bubbling)
Huh?
Day's turning into night.
That's part of the veil.
Since there's a
residential area nearby,
we use it to conceal us
from those on the outside.
Awesome.
Moron
-Demon dogs.
-(Dog bubbling)
(Dog howling)
He'll let us know if
the curse gets close.
Good boy, buddy.
What a good boy.
You know, we're
all counting on you.
(door creaking)
Let's go
(footsteps clicking)
Hold up.
(gasping) what the hell is this?
What's going on here?
I thought this was only a two
story dorm building, isn't it?
Well, maybe it's
a condo, chill out.
[Megumi] No, it's not.
It's the deployment
of an innate domain
due to cursed energy, I've
never seen one this big before.
The door.
Hey, it's gone.
Impossible.
No way, we just came
through that door a second ago.
[Both] What do we
do, what do we do,
-its a major problem.
-[Megumi] We'll be fine.
The dog remembers
the scent of the entrance.
[Both] Oh, good.
-Good dog, good dog
boy -Good boy, good boy.
-Whose a good boy, huh,
-Now you can have all the
-Oh that's right,
-beef jerky you want.
- (laughing)
-Stop playing around.
You rock Fushiguro,
you're such a pro.
Thanks to you, we can rescue
some people and save ourselves.
Let's keep moving.
(eerie music)
Horrible.
Looks like three victims, right?
[Mother] Where's Tadashi,
I need to know if my
son, Tadashi, is all right.
Let's take this
body back with us,
this is that woman's son.
But.
His face isn't too mangled.
How will she accept his death,
if we can't show her
a body to prove it?
(clothes shuffling)
We still have to find
and verify two more,
leave that body behind.
That makes no sense,
the way we got inside
isn't even there anymore,
we won't be able to
come back for it later.
I didn't say we'd come
back, I said, leave it behind.
I'm not about to risk
my own life for someone
I had no intention of
saving in the first place,
so forget it.
You had no intention
of saving him?
Are you kidding?
It's a juvy detention center
and as a Jujutsu sorcerer,
I had access to
information about this guy.
Tadashi here, hit and killed
a little girl on her
way home from school
while driving without a license.
And that was his second offense.
I know you're keen on this
idea of saving lots of people
and guiding them
to proper deaths,
but think how are
you going to feel
when someone you save goes
on to kill someone else later.
So why'd you bother
saving me then?
You both need to cut it
out (groans in frustration)
What the hell is wrong
with the two of you?
Are you guys both idiots?
This is hardly the time
and place to be acting like
(Nobara splashing)
Kugi.. saki?
[Megumi] No, way,
Demon dogs should
have sensed curse.
(eerie music)
Itadori!!
Time to run.
We'll find her
later, right now...
(both gasping in shock)
[Megumi] No
mistaking it, it's a special grade.
I can't move.
[Yuuji] Move,
move, move, move.
[Grandpa] You're a strong
kid so try to help others.
(sword clanging)
(hand thudding)
Ita... dori...
(gasping in shock)
(footsteps clicking)
Where am I?
It's so dark, I can't see
a damn thing in here.
(chilling tune)
The curse's presence.
How can there be so many?
(air whooshing)
Nue.
(wings whooshing)
(feet thudding)
[Megumi]
Itadori and Kugisaki,
don't you die on me.
[Yuuji]
I can't run away,
not when I've gotten this close.
Hey Sukuna, if I die here
then you die too, right?
So you have to help me out.
[Sukuna] Not true.
Even if the part of me
that's inside, you dies.
There are 18 other fragments
of my soul still out there,
still irritatingly enough,
I don't yet have
control of this body.
So if you want to switch,
go ahead and switch.
But once you do, I'll
kill this punk sorcerer
before the curse spirit can.
And then I'll do the
woman, she's a lively one,
I'll have some fun with her.
I'm not gonna let you do that.
[Sukuna] Is that right?
But if you get all focused on me
then your friends are gonna die.
(curse inhaling deeply)
(ground rumbling)
[Megumi] That's not Jujutsu,
he just unleashed
pure cursed energy.
(curse laughing)
Fushiguro, Fushiguro, Fushiguro.
Find Kugisaki and
get her out of here.
I'll stay here and
keep this one busy,
at least until
you two are clear.
As soon as you're both out,
give me some kind of signal
and then I'll switch
bodies with Sukuna.
[Megumi] You'll
never stand a chance.
Finding that thing
with one hand?
Look closer, the
curse is having fun.
It's obviously toying with us.
At least I can buy us some time.
You can't.
Kushiguro, it's okay.
-Demon dogs -(dog whooshing)
Find Kugisaki.
(curses laughing)
Down to my last one already.
I guess I should have brought
a few more of
them along with me.
(clothes ripping)
(curse laughing)
Guess you're saying it's
easier to move around,
stripped down to your underwear.
[Yuuji] What
am I supposed to do?
I have no idea how
to use cursed energy.
For now, that's fine.
I just have to buy some time.
(power whooshing)
What the hell was that?
A cursed energy barrier?
(high frequency vibration)
(ground rumbling)
(groaning in pain)
(heavy thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(light zapping)
(ground rumbling)
(power zapping)
(groaning in pain)
Ow, Ow, Ow.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
Why am I doing this?
If only I hadn't picked
up that finger back then.
If only I hadn't eaten it.
If only, if only.
Stop it, don't think.
No, no, I wanna run, I
wanna run, I wanna run.
I don't wanna die.
If I died here,
if I actually died,
would that be a proper death?
(light zapping)
Don't think.
[Grandpa] So,
try to help others.
(ground booming)
Have I, have I gotten so weak?
You, I know your face now.
I swear, I'm going to curse you.
(curse groaning)
(frog croaking)
We're out here now, let's go.
You know, I really hate frogs.
Well, that's too damn bad.
I was so proud, I thought
I was really strong.
At least strong enough
that I could choose
when and how I die, but I'm not.
I'm weak.
I'm way too weak.
I don't wanna die
but I am gonna die.
No way, not like this.
No (sobbing)
Not like this (sobbing)
[Yuuji]
A proper death,
yeah, right, don't be naive.
[Man] Jujutsu sorceress
never die without regret.
[Yuuji] Still,
I wanna be able to say
my death was a proper one.
[Man] These negative
emotions of mankind
become a source of curses.
[Yuuji] So,
all the hate, the fear,
the regret, let it all out
-and put it in your fist.
-(fire crackling)
(curse laughing)
(soothing music)
Damn, nothing.
(dog howling)
[Yuuji] The howl.
[Yuuji] That must
be the signal from Kushiguro.
(face whooshing)
[Sukuna] Incredible,
what a pain this brat is.
(upbeat music)
Incredible, what
a pain this brat is.
It's obvious he's just
screwing around with me.
Hold on a minute,
I'm thinking here.
What I need, is some
way to make him regret
doing all of this.
[Sukuna]
Nah, if I went after him,
the punk would
just switch right back.
So the thing that would
cause him the most trouble,
is probably this.
I'll just put things
back the way they were.
All right, let's
go kill some kids.
Follow me.
(curse roaring)
Idiot.
Oh, shit I healed
his other hand too.
(curse gasping in shock)
What, you don't
like to take walks?
Well, that's true.
Cursed spirits are
usually supposed to stay
where they're born.
Fine, fine, in that case,
you will die here.
(curse groaning in pain)
Hey, what's the matter.
You're not finished
already, are you?
(groaning in effort)
Yeah good, that's the
way, just try a little harder.
(ground rumbling)
(air whooshing)
Even a cursed spirit is
bound to miss his arm.
(teeth gnashing)
(Sukuna laughing)
(water splashing)
[Megumi] You need to
expand the evacuation area
to 10 kilometers.
[Kitoyaka] What about you?
I'll stay, I'm going
to wait for Itadori.
Understood, all right,
let me get Kugisaki
to the hospital.
Then I'll come back here of you.
No, you wouldn't be of that
much use in this situation.
To really help, you could
have them send us a sorcerer
whose grade one or higher.
If one was around.
I'll do my best, later.
[Megumi]
Even if this goes south,
if the worst case happens.
I don't want him to die?
Gojou, can you save him?
It will be my
responsibility to end him.
Hey, did you know about this?
Surprisingly, you and I both
are apparently classified
as special grade.
Good job, you and me, man.
(curse bubbling)
All right, special grade.
You just keep trying.
(curse laughing)
Pleased with yourself?
You want praise now?
But healing with cursed
energy, isn't all that difficult.
It's a lot easier for cursing
spirits than it is for humans.
Neither you nor this
punk whose body I'm in,
truly understand
what curses really are.
This is a good opportunity.
So I will use it to show you
exactly what real Jujutsu is.
Domain expansion.
-Malevolent shrine.
-(eerie music)
(curse splattering)
I was only planning
to slice you into three
but I guess you were
weaker than I thought.
Oh yeah and then there's this.
I will be taking this.
(fire whooshing)
It's over you punk.
What are you waiting for,
if you're gonna switch
then do it already.
Oh, oh, something wrong brat?
(laughing)
Well, well.
(Closing Theme Music)
(Nobara, Megumi
and Yuuji) Juju Stroll
Yes, yes I understand.
Yes, indeed, thank
you very much.
Yes.
What's the matter?
You bow even when
you're talking on the phone?
(laughing) Well,
when I'm on a call
I get so wrapped up
in talking to that person
that it feels like
they're really there.
Oh, I get that, I've even
hurt my neck before,
dealing with those
damn ingrown hairs
while I was depilating,
what's worse,
I've damaged my pores.
That's not even
remotely the same.
You always sound pissed
off when you're on the phone,
Fushiguro.
That's because of Gojou,
it's not because of the phone.
Itadori, when you're on
the phone, you walk around.
Speaking of phones,
I bet you can't stay on a call
while holding
your phone like this.
(bell ringing)
(Nobara gasping)
-(Nobara screaming)
-(phone shattering)
(upbeat music)